{
    "name": "The Great Test Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Did you answer this test question correctly?",
            "options": [
                "Nope",
                "Doubt it",
                "Of course!",
                "This question confuses me"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Are you ready (John Anderson voice)?",
            "options": [
                "Always",
                "Not yet",
                "Does it matter",
                "Option D"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "When was the first ever release of Python?",
            "options": [
                "June 1992",
                "October 1993",
                "February 1991",
                "January 1994"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What version was that release?",
            "options": [
                "0.7.2",
                "0.9.0",
                "0.8.0",
                "1.0.0"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "So, when was 1.0 released?",
            "options": [
                "June 1992",
                "October 1993",
                "February 1991",
                "January 1994"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "What does this do? `def a(b, c, d): pass`",
            "options": [
                "defines a list and initializes it",
                "defines a function, which does nothing",
                "defines a function, which passes its parameters through",
                "defines an empty class"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What symbol can you use to comment out one line of code?",
            "options": [
                "//",
                "\"",
                "#",
                "$"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What exception is thrown from `int('a')`?",
            "options": [
                "SyntaxError",
                "CastError",
                "RuntimeError",
                "ValueError"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "In PEP-8, what does error code E501 indicate?",
            "options": [
                "Unexpected indentation",
                "Line too long",
                "Blank line at end of file",
                "Too many puppies"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What does `type(print)` return?",
            "options": [
                "function",
                "classobj",
                "Nothing, it raises `RuntimeError`",
                "Nothing, it raises `SyntaxError`"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Given a class instance `b` what does `type(b.__module__)` return?",
            "options": [
                "str",
                "depends where the class was defined",
                "instance",
                "depends where the instance was instantiated"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Did you enjoy this quiz?",
            "options": [
                "Only a little",
                "Not at all",
                "Immensely, without a shadow of a doubt",
                "Can I go home?"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        }
    ]
}
